[Music]
now let's have a little introduction
like pharmaceuticals agrochemicals
explosives
rubber chemicals and coloring substances
etc
manufacturing facilities
[Music]
japan and europe included
india was sixth largest producer at
chemicals car globally
and third largest in asia and the indian
chemical industry is expected to double
by the year 2025.
frequently disruptions
infrastructure agriculture etc
foreign
category
let's
anything about 15 to 20 percent i think
is decent or good
and year after year i see growth
maintained at the hs oximeter that's
what i think
though in the past two years the sales
growth rate is more than 20 percent
which is good 2017 2018 may come
so
this figure shows us that
the u.s companies but the average is
around 10 percent so we should look for
15 to 20 percent
or more in great stocks 2020
so overall i think these figures are not
bad
up the next thing that i find very
interesting is personal investment by
the board of directors in the company
leadership team company
is 2 crores 18 lakhs 79 831 shares
which is a big number
investing
a
government of gujarat and he has also
been a director on the central board of
reserve bank of india
from 2016 to 2020.
institute of science education and
research
that i find about the company so the
first positive is that the company
manufactures a diversified range of
chemicals
starting in the chat sodium nitrate but
over the years independently product
range for diversified gear
supply
a group
about the company
but after that you might need to
consider this factor as well
and my personal enjoy long term
investments my belief
i believe the best way to generate
wealth in share markets is to invest in
good companies and good businesses for a
long term
generally three to five years and that
is what i think is the best way to
generate wealth and share markets
so that's it for today i hope your
[Music]
videos
and don't forget to share it with those
who you think might benefit from it
bye and take care